const questions = {
  questions:[
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'ku',
      font: 'kulitan',
      options: ['Ku', 'Bu', 'Ba', 'Da'],
      correctAnswer: 'baa',
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'kuu',
      options: ['Ge', 'Sang', 'Kú-Kû', 'Yang' ],
      correctAnswer: 'Kú-Kû',
    },
{
  id: 3,
  question: 'laa',
  options: ['Mo', 'Lá-Lâ', 'Kú-Kû', 'Sang' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Lá-Lâ',
},
{
  id: 4,
  question: 'lang',
  options: ['Mang', 'Lang', 'Tang', 'Gang' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Lang',
},
{
  id: 5,
  question: 'le',
  options: ['Le', 'Mi', 'Dá-Dâ', 'Lu' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Le',
},
{
  id: 6,
  question: 'li',
  options: ['Ku', 'Bu', 'Li', 'Lu' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Li',
},
{
  id: 7,
  question: 'lii',
  options: ['Dá-Dâ', 'Lí-Lî', 'Ba', 'Be' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Lí-Lî',
},
  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'lo',
    options: ['Ga', 'Lo', 'Wa', 'Ye' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Lo',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: 'lu',
    options: ['Lu', 'Yang', 'Ke', 'Da' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Lu',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'luu',
    options: ['Yu', 'Ku', 'Lú-Lû', 'Lu' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Lú-Lû',
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: 'maa',
    options: ['Mo', 'Má-Mâ', 'Ma', 'Ka' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Má-Mâ',
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: 'Mang',
    options: ['Mang', 'Sang', 'Pang', 'Ki' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Mang',
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: 'me',
    options: ['Be', 'Ngi', 'Me', 'Mi' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Me',
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: 'Mi',
    options: ['Di', 'Mi', 'Ki', 'Si' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Mi',
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: 'mii',
    options: ['Du', 'Pu', 'Gu', 'Mí-Mî' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Mí-Mî',
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: 'mo',
    options: ['Lo', 'We', 'Wu', 'Mo' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Mo',
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: 'mu',
    options: ['Mu', 'Dú-Dû', 'Gu', 'Tu' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Mu',
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: 'muu',
    options: ['Mang', 'Mú-Mû', 'Bang', 'Ko' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Mú-Mû',
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: 'naa',
    options: ['Ki', 'Mú-Mû', 'Ná-Nâ', 'Ya' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ná-Nâ',
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: 'nang',
    options: ['Go', 'Wa', 'Nang', 'Se' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Nang',
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: 'ne',
    options: ['Bi', 'Ne', 'Ga', 'Mo' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ne',
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: 'ngang',
    options: ['Pang', 'Nga', 'Tang', 'Lu' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ngang',
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: 'ngaa',
    options: ['Ngang', 'Mang', 'Yang', 'Ngá-Ngâ' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ngá-Ngâ',
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: 'nge',
    options: ['Nge', 'Gí-Gî', 'Bi', 'So' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Nge',
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: 'ngi',
    options: ['Pi', 'Ngi', 'Ni', 'Yi' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ngi',
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: 'ngii',
    options: ['Ngí-Ngî', 'Bo', 'Sang', 'Pe' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ngí-Ngî',
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: 'ngo',
    options: ['Pu', 'Ngo', 'Dang', 'Ko' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ngo',
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: 'ngu',
    options: ['Nga', 'Pu', 'Da', 'Ngu' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ngu',
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: 'nguu',
    options: ['Bang', 'Kí-Kî', 'Ngú-Ngû', 'Pa' ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ngú-Ngû',
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question: 'ni',
    options: ['Ni', 'Si', 'Pi', 'Gi' ],
    correctAnswer: 'ni',
  },

  ]
  };
  
  export default questions;